discountsstory.net 2014-09-20

# Privacy Policy - DiscountsStory.net

#### Privacy Statement

DiscountsStory is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our offerings. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. This Privacy Statement only covers the site DiscountsStory.

#### Aggregated Information

Aggregated information, such as which page users access or visit, and information volunteered by users is collected through various methods. For example, DiscountsStory collects IP addresses; an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web. Web servers (the computers that "serve up" Web pages) automatically identify your computer by its IP address; when you request a page from DiscountsStory, our servers log your IP address. 

DiscountsStory only uses IP addresses for the purposes of Web traffic analysis and trends.

#### Use of Information

DiscountsStory collect, store, share and use information collected from third parties. While we do not collect or store password from third-party service providers, we may receive or store tokens, which allow us to link your DiscountsStory account with the third-party service provider. We utilize the information we collect about our users to learn more about how they interact with our Services to customize the Services to their interests and enhance the user experience. Other websites that may be accessible through links from our Services may have their own privacy statements and personal information collection, use, and disclosure practices. Our merchants and business partners also have their own privacy statements, too. DiscountsStory undertakes to work with third parties who protect and respect your privacy.

#### Use of Cookies

DiscountsStory uses cookies for this site. A cookie is a small data file that most major websites write to your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies allow DiscountsStory to measure activity on the site and to improve your user experience, for example by remembering your passwords and viewing preferences.

#### Children and Privacy

DiscountsStory encourages parents and guardians to spend time with their children online, and to be fully familiar with the sites visited by their children.

#### Individuals under 13

No information should be submitted on DiscountsStory by users under the age of 13 years without consent of their parent or guardian. DiscountsStory does not provide any personally-identifying information for users under the age of 13, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever unless disclosed during collection. 

#### Links to Other Sites

DiscountsStory contains links to sites other than DiscountsStory; those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as DiscountsStory. 

#### Effect of Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or legal rights in or on behalf of any party. DiscountsStory reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time and users will be notified of any changes made.

**USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR CONSENT TO THIS ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE.**
